BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/019
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code no.811835: Waterbury City Board of Education (teachers) and Waterbury Teachers Association, 1996-2007 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Code no.811836: New York City Police Dept. (detectives) and Detectives Endownment Association, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Code no.811837: New York City Health & Hospital Corporation (staff nurses) and New York State Nurses Association, DC 37-420, 1987-2005 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Code no.811838: New York City Police Dept. (sergeants) and Sergeant's Benevolent Association, 1990-2003 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Code no.811839: New York City Police Department (patrolmen) and Police & Patrolmen Association, 1987-2003 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Code no.811840: New York City Health & Hospital Corporation (interns & residents) and Committee of Interns and Residents / Service Employees International Union, Local 1957, 1984-2005 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Code no.811843: Los Angeles City Dept of Power & Water (clerical) and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 18, 1996-2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Code no.811845: District of Columbia (police) and Fraternal Order of Police, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Code no.811846: Los Angeles City Dept of Power & Water (operation, maintenance, service) and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 18, 1996-2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Code no.811847: Phoenix (laborers) and Laborers' International Union of North America, Local 1297, 1987-2007 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Code no.811850: Baltimore City (police dept. unit 1) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 35, 1991-2003 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Code no.811851: Columbus, City of (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 67, 1990-2004 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Code no.811853: Las Vegas City (police) and International Union of Police Associations / Las Vegas Police Protective Association, Local 23, 1996-2001 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Code no.811855: Anchorage School District (teachers & certificated) and National Education Association, Local 4425, 1994- 2000 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Code no.811857: Moreno Valley CA Unified Schools (certificated) and National Education Association / Moreno Valley Education Association, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Code no.811858: Orange CA Unified Schools (classified) and Service Employees International Union / California School Employees Association, Ch. 67, 1995-2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Code no.811859: Orange CA Unified Schools (teachers) and National Education Association / Orange Unified Education Association, 2006- 2001 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Code no.811861: Seattle (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 27, 1991-2004 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Code no.811863: Chicago, City of (drivers) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1993-1999 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Code no.811865: Cleveland, City of (patrol officers) and Cleveland Police Patrolmen's Association, 1992-1998 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Code no.811868: Chicago, City of (police) Lodge 7 and Fraternal Order of Police, 1991-2003 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Code no.811869: San Antonio (fire dept.) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 624, 1995-2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Code no.811870: Flint Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / United Teachers of Flint, 2000-2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Code no.811871: New Bedford MA (teachers) and New Bedford Educators Association, 1996-2002 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Code no.811872: Oklahoma City Board of Education (support) and American Federation of Teachers / Oklahoma City Federation of Classified Employees, Local 4574, 1990-2001 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Code no.811873: Oklahoma City Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Oklahoma City Federation of Teachers, Local 2309, 1993-2002 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Code no.811874: Indianapolis (police) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 86, 1995-2004 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Code no.811876: New York City Police Dept. (police lieutenants) and LBACNY-I, 1995-2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Code no.811877: Tucson Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / Tucsan Education Association, 2001- 2007 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Code no.811878: Aurora County CO (teachers) and National Education Association / Aurora Education Association, 1993-2005 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Code no.820009: Milwaukee County (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 48, 1989- 2001 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Code no.820010: Milwaukee County Transit System (general labor) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 998, 1993-2001 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Code no.820013: Cook County (registered & instructional nurses) and Illinois Nurses Association, 1993-2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Code no.820024: Los Angeles County (administrative & technical-unit 121) and Service Employees International Union, Local 660, 1997-2003 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Code no.820048: Dade County (general classified) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 199, 1990- 2005 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Code no.820073: Cuyahoga County (welfare employees) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1746, 1983-2008 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Code no.820074: Prince Georges County MD (police) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 89, 1999-2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Code no.820075: Baltimore City public schools (warehouse, drivers) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 37 & 44, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Code no.820076: Indianapolis Board of Schools Comm (operations) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 661, 1997-2001 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Code no.820077: Cook County (hospital technicians) and Service Employees International Union, Local 73, 1984-2001 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Code no.820078: Marin County CA (units 1-5 & 16) and Service Employees International Union / Marin Association of Public Employees, Local 949, 1998-2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Code no.820080: New York City Health & Hospital Corporation (institutional services) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1995-2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Code no.820082: Maryland (law enforcement--unit I) and The State Law Enforcement Officers Labor Alliance, 1998-2003 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Code no.820083: Oregon State (corrections--nonsecurity) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 2001- 2003 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Code no.820084: Minneapolis Public Schools (educational assistants) and American Federation of Teachers, MFEA 59, 1998- 2003 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Code no.820144: MetroHealth Medical Centers (nonprofessionals) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 3360, Local 3353, 1995-2004 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Code no.820145: Mamii-Dade County public schools (supervisors) and American Federation of School Administrators, Local 77, 1998- 2003 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Code no.820148: Suffolk County (white collar-unit 2) and Suffolk County Association of Municipal Employees, 1989-2000 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Code no.820152: Los Angeles County (dep probation officers-unit 701) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1992-2003 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Code no.820153: Frederick County MD Board of Education (support) and Frederick Association of School Support Employees, 1995- 2004 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Code no.820154: Denver School District No 1 (paraprofessionals) and American Federation of Teachers / Denver Federation for Paraprofessionals, 1997-2006 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Code no.820155: San Francisco Unified School Distrtict (b/c, w/c) and Service Employees International Union, Local 790, 1997- 2000 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Code no.820156: Elk Grove Unified School District (classified) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 258, 2000-2003 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Code no.820157: Elk Grove Unified School District (certficated) and National Education Association / Elk Grove Education Association, 2000- 2001 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Code no.820161: Onondaga County (multiunit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 834, 1977- 1989 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Code no.820175: Los Angeles County (paramedical technical-unit 221) and Service Employees International Union, Local 660, 1997- 2003 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Code no.820191: Los Angeles County (social service investigators-unit 731) and Service Employees International Union, Local 660, 1997- 2003 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Code no.820192: Beaverton OR School District 48 (classified) and Oregon School Employees Association, Ch. 48, 1983-1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Code no.820210: San Diego County (AE, CL, FS, MM, PR, PS, SS units) and Service Employees International Union, Local 2028, 1996- 2001 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Code no.820211: Riverside County CA (professional, crafts & b-c) and Laborers' International Union of North America / Union of Professional Employees, Local 777, 1993-2003 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Code no.820213: Niagara County NY (white collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1970- 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Code no.820215: Los Angeles County (artisan & blue collar-unit 431) and Service Employees International Union, Local 660, 1997- 2003 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Code no.820216: Los Angeles County (custodians-unit 201) and Service Employees International Union, Local 660, 1991-1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Code no.820218: Los Angeles County (RNs-unit 311) and Service Employees International Union, 1991-2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Code no.820219: Los Angeles County (health science professional-unit 341) and Service Employees International Union, Local 660, 1991- 1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Code no.820220: Los Angeles County (firefighters-unit 601) and International Association of Fire Fighters, 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Code no.820222: Los Angeles County (building, trades-unit 411) and Building and Construction Trades Council, 1987-1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Code no.820223: Los Angeles City (professional, engineering, & scientific unit) and Engineers and Architects Association, 1994- 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Code no.820224: New Jersey University of Medicine & Dentistry (supervisors) and Communication Workers of America, Local 1031, 1996-2002 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Code no.820232: San Diego County (deputy sheriffs) and San Diego County Deputy Sheriffs Association, 1993-2003 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Code no.820233: Washington, University of (clerical nonsupervisory, media supervisory) and Service Employees International Union / Classified Staff Association, Dist. 925, 1994-2005 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Code no.820235: Riverside County CA (law enforcement) and Riverside Sheriffs Association, 1993-2001 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Code no.820236: San Diego City (blue collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 127, 1993- 2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Code no.820237: San Diego City (firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 145, 1994-2005 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Code no.820238: San Diego City (police) and Police Officers Association, 1993-2005 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Code no.820239: San Diego City (white collar) and Municipal Employees Association, 1994-2005 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Code no.820240: Trenton Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association, 1995-2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Code no.820241: Miami (sworn police) and Police Benevolent Association, Lodge 20, 1995-2001 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Code no.820242: Miami (general employees) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1907, 1995- 2004 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Code no.820251: Burlington County Board of Freeholders (multiunit) and Communication Workers of America, Local 1034, 1995- 2002 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Code no.820255: Orange County CA (general unit) and Orange County Employees Association, 1994-2004 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Code no.820256: Kent County MI (general employees) and United Auto Workers, Local 2600, 1998-2003 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Code no.820257: Washington State (corrections) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 313, 1993-2005 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Code no.820265: Westmoreland County PA (multi-unit) and Service Employees International Union, Local 585, 1988-2001 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Code no.820266: Leon County FL Board of Education (support personnel) and National Education Association / Leon Educational Support Personnel Association, 1999-2003 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Code no.820272: Dade County (police & corrections officers) and Police Benevolent Association, 1993-1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Code no.820287: Nashville & Davidson County, Metro Govt of (multi-unit) and Service Employees International Union, Local 25, 1994-2001 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Code no.820289: Rensselaer County NY (general unit) and United Public Service Employees Union, Local 424, 1994-2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Code no.820290: New York City (custodial employees) and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 94, 1982-1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Code no.820292: Montgomery County OH (full-time employees) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / DPSU 101, 1996-2003 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Code no.820297: Los Angeles County (peace officers-unit 611) and Association for Los Angeles Deputy Sheriffs, 1988-1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Code no.820298: Los Angeles County (supervisory peace officers-unit 612) and International Union of Police Associations / Professional Peace Officers Association, 1995-1995 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Code no.820311: San Diego County (welfare unit) and Service Employees International Union, Local 535, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Code no.820318: Cook County (clerical in hospitals) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees. Co. 31, 1993- 2001 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Code no.820319: Chicago, City of (white-collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 31, 1992- 1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Code no.820320: New Jersey Transit Business Operations (operations & maintenance) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Locals 819-825, 880, 1993-2005 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Code no.820321: Rhode Island State (corrections officers) and Rhode Island Brotherhood of Corrections Officers, 1997-2003 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Code no.820322: Rhode Island State (social workers) and Service Employees International Union / Rhode Island Alliance of Social Service Employees, Local 580, 1986-2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Code no.820325: Los Angeles County (child social workers-unit 723) and Service Employees International Union, Local 535, 1991- 1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Code no.820338: Nassau County NY (police dept.) and Police Benevolent Association, 1982-1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Code no.820344: Westchester County (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 860, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Code no.820346: Westchester County (nurses) and New York State Nurses Association, 1975-1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Code no.820348: Erie County NY (white collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 815, 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Code no.820349: Erie County NY (blue collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1095, 1995- 1999 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Code no.820350: Chataqua County NY (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 807, 1990-2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Code no.820351: Saratoga County (blue and white collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, 1995-1999 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Code no.820356: Suffolk County (police dept.) and Police Benevolent Association, 1976-1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Code no.820359: Wayne County MI (sheriff's department) and Service Employees International Union, Local 502, 1986-2004 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Code no.820365: Dutchess County NY (multiunit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 814, 1987-2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Code no.820377: Monroe County NY (multiunit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 828, 1994-2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Code no.820383: Ulster County NY (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees/ Civil Service Employees Association, 1992-2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Code no.820384: Orange County NY (County employees unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 1000, Local 836, 1986-1999 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Code no.820389: Broome County (white collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 1000, 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Code no.820418: Wishard Health Services (health care wrkrs) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2065, 1994-2001 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Code no.820419: Palm Beach County (blue collar) and Communication Workers of America, Local 3181, 1994-2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Code no.820420: Lake County FL School Board (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Lake County Education Association, Local 3783, 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Code no.820421: Collier County FL School Board (teachers) and National Education Association, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Code no.820436: Los Angeles County (Interns & residents-unit 323) and Joint Council of Interns & Residents, 1991- 1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Code no.820450: Hennepin County MN (social services unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 34, 1995-2007 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Code no.820456: Hennepin County MN (clerical unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2822, 2000-2007 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Code no.820464: Schenectady County (general) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 847, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Code no.820469: Kern County CA (general unit) and Service Employees International Union, Local 700, 1996-2003 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Code no.820486: Los Angeles County (office & clerical-unit 111) and Service Employees International Union, Local 660, 2000- 2003 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Code no.820489: Dade County (fire fighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 1403, 2000-2003 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Code no.820490: Milwaukee County (nurses) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 5002, 1984-1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Code no.820496: Los Angeles County (clerical supervisors-unit 112) and Service Employees International Union, Local 660, 1997- 2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Code no.820527: Contra Costa County CA (clerical & office) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2700, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Code no.820528: Contra Costa County CA (multiunit) and Contra Costa County Employees Association, Local 1, 1993-1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Code no.820535: Rockland County NY (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 1000, 1993-2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Code no.820537: Ventura County CA (general unit) and Service Employees International Union, Local 998, 1992-2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Code no.820541: Wayne County MI (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 25, Local 101, Local 409, Local 1659, 1993-2000 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Code no.820578: Sonoma County CA (general unit) and Service Employees International Union / Sonoma County Organization of Public Employees, Local 707, 1996-2008 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Code no.820584: San Bernardino County (general unit) and San Bernardino Public Employees Association, 1977-1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Code no.820586: Santa Cruz County CA (general unit) and Service Employees International Union, Local 415, 1983-2002 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Code no.820607: Merced County CA (units 4, 5, 6 & 8) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2703, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Code no.820608: Niagara Frontier Transit (operations & maintenance; clerical & office) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1342, 1990-2000 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Code no.820609: San Mateo County (clerical and technical) and Service Employees International Union, Local 715, 1996-2002 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Code no.820610: San Mateo County (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 829, 1996- 2002 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Code no.820635: Monterey County CA (general unit-j unit) and Service Employees International Union, Local 817, 1993-2003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Code no.820640: New Rochelle public schools (teachers and others) and American Federation of Teachers/ New York State United Teachers, Local 280, 1996-2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Code no.820670: Riverside County CA (supporting services) and Service Employees International Union, Local 1997, 1993-2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Code no.820696: San Joaquin County (paraprofessionals & technical) and Service Employees International Union, Local 790, 1994-2003 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Code no.820698: San Joaquin County (office, technical, & clerical) and Service Employees International Union, Local 790, 1992- 2004 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Code no.820722: Fresno County (clerical, paramedical-unit12) and Service Employees International Union, Local 535, 1979-1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Code no.820737: Nassau County NY (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 830, 1998-2002 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Code no.820785: Hamilton County TN Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / Hamilton County Education Association, 1994-2001 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Code no.820788: Baltimore County Board of Education (maintenance & operations) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 434, 1995-2002 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Code no.820789: Baltimore County Board of Education (clerical) and National Education Association / Baltimore Association of Clerical Employees, 1995-2003 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Code no.820790: Baltimore County Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / Teachers Association of Baltimore County, 1985-2003 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Code no.820791: Hillsborough County FL Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / Hillsborough County Teachers Association, 1998-2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Code no.820792: Orange County CA (office service) and Orange County Employees Association, 1994-2004 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Code no.820793: Alameda County CA (multidepartment unit) and Service Employees International Union, Local 250, Local 535, Local 616, 1989-2000 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Code no.820794: Jackson Hospital Public Health Trust (nurses) and Service Employees International Union, 1983-2002 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Code no.820795: Sacramento County (office- technical) and Sacramento County Employees Organization, 1988-2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Code no.820796: Kent State University (faculty tenure) and American Association of University Professors, Kent Chapter, 1995- 2004 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Code no.820803: Escambia County FL School District (blue collar) and Florida Teaching Profession - National Education Association, 1986- 2001 (Box 19, Folder 3)